I don't even go shopping for food anymore.
我现在连去超市买吃的都不去了。
I just order it on my laptop online, on my ever-increasing tummy, just lying in bed.
我就躺在床上，把越来越大的肚子当桌子，放着电脑，直接在网上下单。
Bring me this food, bring me that food.
把这个送来，把那个也送来。
Then you click a time slot and they just show up at your house.
然后你选一个送货时间，他们就直接出现在你家门口。
You open the door, they're like, would you like me to bring it in?
你打开门，他们会问："需要我帮您搬进去吗？"
I'm like, ideally, can you feed me?
我心想，最好还能直接喂我吃。
I mean, what services do you offer?
我是说，你们到底提供哪些服务啊？
Although at least when you don't go to the supermarket, it means you don't eat on the way round it.
不过至少，不去超市的话，就不会一边逛一边偷吃了。
Because I'm always too greedy, we've all done this.
因为我实在太嘴馋了，不过这种事大家都干过。
You don't own it yet, you don't own the food, but you consume it.
食物还没买下来、还不属于你，但你已经把它吃了。
And then you have that horrible moment of confession, with the till, when you have to just present wrappers.
接着就到了那个令人尴尬的"坦白时刻"——站在收银台前，只能把包装纸递给收银员。
I'm terribly sorry.
真的非常抱歉。
I have this Mars bar, I have the packaging.
我这根玛氏巧克力已经吃完了，只剩包装。
Can you get the information from the packaging?
你能根据包装上的信息结账吗？
Because the Mars bar itself is in my tummy.
因为巧克力本身已经在我肚子里了。
I'll pay you back.
我会把钱补给你的。
I appear to have eaten this lasagna.
我好像把这份千层面也吃掉了。
Will I be very sick?
我不会吃出毛病吧？
It just looks so yummy on the photo.
它照片上看起来实在太诱人了。
Would you like a bag, sir? I just need a bin.
先生，需要袋子吗？ 我只需要一个垃圾桶。
There are many different supermarket options.
超市有很多不同的选择。
I don't know where you shop.
我不知道你们平时在哪家超市买东西。
My wife likes to shop at Waitrose.
我妻子喜欢去 Waitrose 买东西。
It's the middle class option.
那是中产阶级最爱的选择。
People are whooping Waitrose.
人们一提到 Waitrose 就欢呼。
And what they're doing, ladies and gentlemen, is they're just telling you all that they can afford Waitrose. And they love to do it.
女士们、先生们，他们其实就是在告诉大家："我买得起 Waitrose。" 而且他们特别喜欢这样做。
People who shop at Waitrose, they like to drop it into conversations.
去 Waitrose 买东西的人，总喜欢把这件事不经意地带进聊天里。
Sorry I'm late, I was just at Waitrose! "
不好意思迟到了，我刚刚在 Waitrose 买东西！"
Just so everybody knows that they can afford Waitrose.
就是为了让大家知道他们买得起 Waitrose。
Even though they sell basically all the same stuff as other supermarkets.
虽然它卖的基本上和其他超市是同样的东西。
But they just put the prices up so people can feel good about themselves. I'm shopping at Waitrose! Yeah.
但他们只是把价格抬高，好让顾客觉得自己身份更高一点。 毕竟是在 Waitrose 买东西嘛！是吧。
But they like to justify it, you know, the poshies.
不过这些"上流人士"总喜欢替自己找理由。
You know, Waitrose, it's fabulous. " The food is just wonderful, you know. "
你知道吗，Waitrose 真是太棒了。 那里的食物真的太好了。"
It's organic. "
都是有机食品。"
It's beyond organic, you know. "
甚至已经超越有机了。"
The chickens, they just sacrifice themselves. "
那些鸡都是主动献身的。"
They just walk up.
它们自己就走过来了。
They walk up to the main entrance.
它们径直走到正门口。
Hi, this is my family. And we just… I bought some condiments, do what you like. Just take me, take me.
你好，这是我的家人。 我们就……我还带了点调味料，你们想怎么处理我都行。 带我走吧，带我走吧。
And I'd never seen anybody return the trolley for the pound in the car park in Waitrose.
我从没见过有人在 Waitrose 停车场为了那一英镑押金去还购物车。
It's simply not worth it to them.
对他们来说，这根本不值得。
You see them coming out with their trolleys, looking for their Range Rovers. Which one is mine?
你会看到他们推着购物车出来，寻找自己的路虎。 哪辆是我的？"
I think it's this one over here. "
我想应该是这辆。"
Oh, they pop the boot open as well.
哦，他们还会提前把后备箱打开。
You see, once you've got a certain amount of money, this, this, and this, those days are behind you.
你看，一旦有了一定财富，这些事情就已经成为过去了。
Now they have these keys. And you push the key that closes it, that locks it, and then one that opens it, and then a boot one.
现在他们都用这种车钥匙。 钥匙上有锁车键、解锁键，还有一个专门开后备箱的按钮。
And people like to pop it open.
人们特别喜欢提前把它打开。
They don't wait until they get to the car.
他们都不用等走到车旁。
The more posh you are, the further away from the vehicle you pop the boot open.
越是"贵族范儿"，越喜欢离车老远就把后备箱打开。
It can become quite treacherous for other people walking in the car park, because these boots start flying up all over the place.
这对停车场里的其他人来说可能相当危险，因为到处都有后备箱突然弹起来。
People have to walk in a single file.
大家都只能排成一列走。
Okay, kids, just follow me so we don't get hit by the boots. "
孩子们，跟紧我，别被这些后备箱撞到了。"
People doing it at the till.
甚至有人在收银台就开始开后备箱。
People flying into airports going, "Oh, look, there's the car."
甚至有人刚飞到机场，一看到自己的车就说："哦，车在那儿。"
Better pop the boot open. It'll go in easier to get the bags in. "
最好先把后备箱打开，这样待会儿放行李更方便。"
So they get to the Range Rover. They unload their shopping in the back.
于是他们走到自己的路虎旁。 他们把买来的东西放到后备箱。
And then they see the pound. And they think, I should have that.
然后他们看到了那枚一英镑硬币。 他们心想："哦，这一镑还是应该拿回来。"
That's money. I should have that. But I can't.
那可是钱啊，我应该拿回来。可是我懒得去。
It's stuck. "
它还卡着呢。"
And they realise, I've got to go all the way over there and plug it in to the trolley train for a pound.
然后他们意识到，为了一英镑，还得一路走过去，把购物车插回购物车队里。
All the way over there and back for a pound.
为了这一镑，还得来回跑一趟。
By the time I got there and back, the house would have made about 15 grand.
等我来回一趟，我家的资产都已经涨了一万五千镑了。
So I didn't really see the point.
所以我觉得根本没必要。
So then they sort of do this push away.
于是他们就轻轻把购物车推走。
They do the Waitrose posh push.
他们来一个典型的"Waitrose 贵族式推车"。
They just pause and go, "Off you go. Goodbye."
他们停顿一下，然后说："去吧，拜拜。"
And then the trolley sort of rolls away and then collides with another Range Rover.
然后购物车慢慢滑走，又撞上另一辆路虎。
That's another posh person to go, "What's that doing there? Off you go."
另一位"贵族人士"又说："这东西怎么会在这？走吧走吧。"
It's normally someone from Aldi in the bushes.
通常最后都是 Aldi 的顾客从灌木丛里把它捡走。
I'll have that. Thank you. "
那我就收下了，谢谢。"
Get my old shopping done on that quid, you idiots. "
靠这一镑，我下次买东西的钱都有了，你们这帮傻瓜。"